# Jon Waaler

### Detail-oriented software developer with 2 years of professional experience

Toronto, ON M4N 2V2 jonwaaler@outlook.com +1 416 912 7235

Programmer with almost 2 years of experience in an fast paced start-up environment managing RemnantLabs' primary product "Alter Genesis" (a video game, Unity3D, C#). I excel at learning new technologies and software on the fly while also maintaining development on the primary product. I have a passion for exploring new and uncomfortable spaces and am looking for opportunities that will expand in that experience.

## Work Experience

#### Game Developer - (Unity3D, C#)

Remnant Lab Inc - Toronto, ON March 2021 to August 2022

- Manage and develop the primary product "Alter Genesis"
- Assisted in raising ~\$1 million USD in private and public investment
- · Provide customer support to 1000s of individuals on Remnant Labs social media platforms
- Learning crypto currency technologies for the integration with our game
- Agile Project Management methodologies

## **Banquet Server & Labor**

BBQ Gourmet - Toronto, ON May 2019 to August 2019

- Packing/unpacking trucks based on an inventory list
- Serve and interact with customers to make sure they have a good experience and enjoy their food

#### **Residence Support**

Simcoe Residence - Ontario Tech University August 2017 to September 2017

- Be friendly, welcome students
- · Help families move luggage
- answer questions, give directions

#### Education

### **Certificate in UofT SCS Coding Boot Camp**

University of Toronto school of continuing education - Toronto, ON February 2021 to April 2021

## Bachelor of Information Technology in Game Development & Entrepreneurship

University of Ontario Institute of Technology

2016 to April 2020

## Skills

- Unity
- C#
- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS
- Node.js
- Git
- React
- MySQL

## Languages

• Spanish - Beginner

## Links

https://jonwaaler.github.io/

https://remnant.gg/

https://remnant.gg/altergenesis